<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/</id><title>Ankush Pratap Singh</title><subtitle>This is the personal bio of Ankush Pratap Singh. I am a computer engineering graduate from New York University with a master's degree. My passion lies in the fields of machine learning, deep learning, and computer vision. With a strong interest in these areas, I strive to explore innovative applications and advancements that drive the future of technology. I am a prospective Phd student.</subtitle> <updated>2024-09-09T09:32:44-04:00</updated> <author> <name>Ankush Pratap Singh</name> <uri>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2024 Ankush Pratap Singh </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>🎓 Starting my PhD Journey 🎉</title><link href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/PhD-Acceptance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🎓 Starting my PhD Journey 🎉" /><published>2024-07-15T06:00:01-04:00</published> <updated>2024-07-15T07:13:08-04:00</updated> <id>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/PhD-Acceptance/</id> <content src="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/PhD-Acceptance/" /> <author> <name>Ankush Pratap Singh</name> </author> <summary> 🌟 Exciting News! 🌟 I’m thrilled to share that I’ve been accepted as a PhD student at New York Institute of Technology New York, starting Fall 2024! I will be diving deep into Computer Science with a focus on Deep Learning and Affective Computing under the guidance of Prof. Houwei Cao. My research will aim to study and develop machines that can recognize, interpret, process, and simulate human... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>🎓 Celebrating the Completion of an Incredible Journey 🎉</title><link href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/MS-Completion/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="🎓 Celebrating the Completion of an Incredible Journey 🎉" /><published>2023-05-19T06:00:01-04:00</published> <updated>2023-05-28T11:19:58-04:00</updated> <id>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/MS-Completion/</id> <content src="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/MS-Completion/" /> <author> <name>Ankush Pratap Singh</name> </author> <summary> When everyone was busy posing for photos after the graduation ceremony, I found myself rushing back home to put the final touches on my thesis report. Now that everything is done and dusted, I’m thrilled to share that I have successfully defended my thesis! 📚 Reflecting on this momentous occasion, I can’t help but reminisce about the incredible years I spent at NYU Tandon School of Engineering... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Exciting News! Thesis Defense Success!</title><link href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/Thesis-Defense/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Exciting News! Thesis Defense Success!" /><published>2023-05-19T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2023-12-26T18:36:56-05:00</updated> <id>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/Thesis-Defense/</id> <content src="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/Thesis-Defense/" /> <author> <name>Ankush Pratap Singh</name> </author> <summary> I am absolutely thrilled to announce that I have successfully defended my thesis! It is with immense joy and gratitude that I share this milestone in my academic journey. After months (and even years) of hard work, research, and dedication, I can finally say that I am officially a proud defender of my thesis! This momentous occasion marks the culmination of countless hours spent poring over li... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Joined AI4CE lab</title><link href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/AI4CE-lab/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Joined AI4CE lab" /><published>2022-09-03T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2022-09-03T06:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/AI4CE-lab/</id> <content src="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/AI4CE-lab/" /> <author> <name>Ankush Pratap Singh</name> </author> <summary> I am very happy to announce that I have joined AI4CE Lab (headed by Prof Chen Feng) and I’ll be doing my research under the guidance of Prof Chen Feng and Chao Chen (Phd student)starting Fall 2022. I’ll be working on the creation, modelling and analysis of different deep learning architectures for Scene Summarization project. </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Joined NYU Video Lab</title><link href="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/NYU-Video-lab/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Joined NYU Video Lab" /><published>2022-09-02T06:00:00-04:00</published> <updated>2022-09-02T06:00:00-04:00</updated> <id>https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/NYU-Video-lab/</id> <content src="https://ankushpratap95.github.io/posts/NYU-Video-lab/" /> <author> <name>Ankush Pratap Singh</name> </author> <summary> I am very happy to announce that I have joined NYU Video Lab (headed by Prof Yao Wang) and I’ll be doing my research under the guidance of Prof Yao Wang and Chris Liu (Phd student)starting Fall 2022. I’ll be working on the creation, modelling and analysis of different deep learning architectures on NYUMets dataset. </summary> </entry> </feed>
